there's a
place in my
heart that I keep for someone
special
Memories Forever true to
me take me through those
tougher
days
suddenly I found in
you all the joy the smiles and
laughter all the hope and love
divine always you you on my mind
I always knew there would be the
day when I give my heart away to the one
who always keep me safe and
warm if I should go I won't ever forget
the special days the times we had and no
matter what where the winds have change
you'll always be
uni in my my
heart where I keep my little
treasure it's a time I always turn
to it's a place where you're by my
side I always knew there would be the
day when I give my heart away to the one
who love always keep me safe and
War if I should go I will never forget
the special days the times we had and no
matter what where the winds are change
you will always be
uniquely
you there's a
place in my heart
that I keep for someone
special it's a time I always turn
to it's the place where you're by my
side you're the special one my only
positive uniquely
w